That's the thing. The love you
showed for the road map video is
infinite.
I read every single comment guys.
Every single one.
Honestly, when I read some comments,
I got goosebumps.
So let me tell you a couple of them.
Bro, I've been searching for a road
map for a month. This is the best
video so far.
Bro, for the same course outside,
they are charging 1 lakh,
1.5 lakh and you are giving
everything for free.
For some people, bro, please don't
stop. This might change my career.
I mean, first of all, thank you to
each and every one of you who
watched this video from the bottom
of my heart.
In the last video, a lot of people
had a lot of doubts and they put all
of those doubts in the comments.
So, summarizing all those doubts,
I'm going to answer each and every
one of them.
So I'm going to answer,
bro, is this course free?
Is it live or recorded?
What's the schedule?
Is it for beginners? Can non -IT
people follow? Where can we get the
resources?
Is there a job guarantee?
Is it in Telugu or English?
I'm going to answer each and every
one of these questions.
First and most asked question,
is this course free?
Yes guys, this course is 100 % free.
I will repeat, this course is 100 %
free.
No payment, no paid batch,
no hidden course, no any other
platform.
Everything will be on YouTube,
recorded videos and live.
So, please come, learn,
enjoy and get your career.
Roadmap website is only the
structure and all the learnings will
be on YouTube.
So you don't have to go anywhere.
Subscribe to the channel,
follow the videos and learn.
Simple.
And the second most important
question, why are you doing this for
free? What are you gaining?
So before answering this question,
I want to tell you one small
personal story.
In 2018, I graduated from NIT
Calicut under Electrical and
Electronics Engineering branch.
Remember this? EEE branch.
It is a non -IT branch.
After that, I got a job in a company
called Infosys. Many of you might
know it.
And my package is 3 LPA at that
time, 3 lakhs per year.
I was grateful. I started my career
because of that company. So I am
grateful to the job.
But the technology I work in is
mainframes, which is very old and
very bad.
I didn't see any future in that.
I was lost. I don't know how to
shape my career.
At the same time, exactly machine
learning, deep learning,
data science boom started well.
Then I started looking at a lot of
people. How to learn, where to
learn, when to learn, what to do.
I was completely lost.
Then at the same time,
I found a mentor.
Srikanth Verma guys. I took his
course.
He taught me machine learning,
deep learning and all the data
science.
But the most important thing is that
he gave me the direction.
And trust me guys, that one roadmap,
that one mentorship changed my
entire career.
Right now, I am here teaching you
guys data science.
Today, if I look back at my journey,
I worked with companies like Warner
Brothers and Discovery,
which is a global company.
I worked with Dosh Telecom,
which is the biggest brand in
Germany.
And right now, I am working in
Netherlands and working for a
company, which is the largest
telecom provider in Switzerland.
So my entire career has changed
because of that one person and that
one course and that one roadmap.
So when I see students and working
professionals like me,
they don't know what to do,
where to start, what to learn.
Because when you learn machine
learning and deep learning,
how it is in the ground,
right now the agent is in the
ground.
And how Srikanth Verma gave me the
direction, I want to be that person
for you.
So if this roadmap, this course and
this channel can change even a few
people's careers, that is more than
enough for me.
And the next one, what I expect from
you, one thing I will say clearly,
I am doing all of this after my full
time job.
I go to work, I do gym,
I do freelance teaching,
I prepare scripts, I record videos,
I edit, I manage my social media.
So if I am giving you 200%,
I will expect something from you as
well, right?
That is seriousness. Free course
means valuable course.
So actually, free course means you
need more discipline because nobody
is forcing you.
So if you are serious,
watch every video, take notes,
practice, write your doubts.
If you have any doubts, you can ask
with me, put it in the comments,
I will reply to each and every one
of the comments.
Build projects, change your career.
So only thing that I expect from you
is full effort from your sides.
From my side, I will put my efforts
200%, I will teach and I will give
you the quality content.
But what to learn, what to practice,
it's up to you.
And the next important question,
course format and schedule.
So after a lot of discussions
internally, I decided that every
alternate day you will get a video.
Let's say Monday, Wednesday and
Friday, 7 PM IST, you will get a
video.
And every Sunday, you will get one
live video for one hour.
If you have any doubts,
you can join the live and you can
ask your queries and I will solve
each and every one of your doubts.
So why this format?
If it is a recorded video,
you can watch anytime.
So you can watch at your own pace
and why live?
I want you to give the experience
like a live course.
That's it, it's not like I can just
record the video and release it.
No, I want to be there for you.
So next question, is this course
suitable for beginners and non -IT
people?
To be honest, it needs a lot of
effort.
I told you a story in the beginning.
I am from a EEE background,
which is a non -IT branch.
And my first job is in mainframes.
I did something right.
I did a lot of practice.
I did a lot of step -by -step
learning.
So I expect the same from you.
So if you are from a non -IT
manufacturing, mechanical,
electrical, chemical, any kind of
branch, you can shift and it is
possible to agentic AI developer.
That is for sure.
But you need basics.
Minimum Python basics.
Python basics, I have covered every
single topic in my YouTube channel.
I have created a playlist called
agentic AI.
I have put all of the videos in that
playlist.
So please go ahead and start
watching these videos.
If you already know the basics of
Python, it's good.
You can continue the series.
If you don't know the Python basics,
please watch this.
I will put the link in the
description below.
Please.
And one more important thing.
Don't compare your day one with
someone else's year three.
Start small, learn step -by -step.
And you can achieve every single
thing.
And the next question.
Is there a job guarantee if you do
this course?
Brutal answer.
I cannot guarantee your job,
guys.
If someone says they will guarantee
me a job, I don't even trust that
person.
Because job depends on many things.
Your practice, your hard work,
your projects, consistency,
your communication, your interview
skills, your existing background,
market condition.
When there are so many factors,
how can I guarantee a job?
How can anyone can guarantee a job?
What I can do is, I can provide you
with the quality content that you
can learn.
So you can crack any kind of
interview.
I can guarantee you that.
But I cannot guarantee job.
So getting a job or not getting a
job, it's entirely up to you.
Telling content, delivering content
with top -notch quality.
That is my part.
I promise you that.
And the next important question.
Where will resources be found?
So in every video I say,
all of that content will be in the
GitHub.
That GitHub link, you will find it
in the description below of every
single video.
In every video I say, every code,
every project, every line,
everything will be open sourced.
And it will be on the GitHub.
So you don't have to go anywhere.
You can view my GitHub and my
channel.
That's it.
And roadmap video will be updated
regularly based on the content that
we cover.
So you will get every single thing
in one place.
And one more thing guys.
Don't become resource collector.
Collecting is not important.
Learn and build from it.
That is what will get you a job.
And next question.
What language?
By default, I will be teaching
everything for free in Telugu.
So why Telugu?
Why can't I do it in English?
I am a Telugu guy.
And I want to give back to the
community that I am from.
I can speak in English and I can
also speak in Hindi.
I can completely make these videos
in Hindi and I can reach to a lot of
people.
But I didn't choose that path.
Because I want to give back to the
community that I am from.
So all the videos will be in Telugu
and with English subtitles.
And don't expect everything in real
Telugu guys.
Because at the end of the day,
when you get interviewed, you need
to speak it in English.
So it's a mix of Telugu and English.
I am doing everything myself.
I am putting a lot of efforts.
So I can guarantee quality content.
But I cannot guarantee fancy editing
guys.
I can't do anything like hooks,
editing, retention in videos.
I can't do it in the time I have.
But what I can promise you is a
quality content.
So from my side, I will deliver
that.
But from your side, I want everyone
to watch the content.
To learn from it.
Don't take it as an entertainment.
Think of it as a career changing
move.
Because ultimately flashy editing
will not get you a job.
Building projects and learning
skills will get you a job.
So this is my final promise guys.
I will teach you everything for free
on YouTube.
I will try to give my best quality.
I will explain it in simple English
and Telugu mix.
I will provide all the resources
whenever it is needed.
I will answer each and every one of
your doubts.
I will help you understand complex
topics easily.
And I will also build you the
mindset of building agents in
production level.
But I also need commitment from me.
If I am doing this much,
I expect something from you as well.
Promise me you will show up.
You will take notes.
You will practice.
You will build.
And you will not give up after two
to three videos.
Because this course is for free.
But not for time passers.
No.
This is only for the serious
learners.
So if you are serious about this
journey.
Please comment something in the
comment section below guys.
So that I know that you are serious.
And like this video.
And do not miss any kind of videos.
Please subscribe.
And one more thing.
If you know someone who needs this
content.
Or who wants this at this phase of
life.
Please share it with them.
If you are a college student.
Please share it in the college
group.
If you are a professional.
Please share it across your friends.
Or professionals who are working
alongside with you.
Or if you know someone.
Who wants to upskill in agent.
Please share it with them.
Because I cannot trust YouTube
recommendations.
But I can trust the word of mouth.
If a friend tells me.
I will believe that.
Right.
So I want that to happen.
So that whoever wants to learn.
They can learn everything for free.
On YouTube.
And at a production level.
It is not for just time passers.
It is for serious learning.
And that's all for this video.
Signing off.
We will meet in the next one.